Okay, let's move on to making clothes.
You can pull the curtain. The curtain should also have a good level, and then the vertical direction.
It's just that the level and the vertical are not good, but you can pull it diagonally. It will be a little better.
I didn't expect it. I even have this knowledge.
Okay, let's make clothes. The clothes are the same. Use the default washing machine, and then the automatic adjustment panel tool.
Automatic adjustment to the appropriate size.
And then when making clothes, we have a formula, which is to reactivate the sleeves first.
That is, you do the big body first, because whether it is a sleeve or a collar, they will interact with the fabric, and they will affect the effect.
So when we are doing it, we must pay attention.
That is, you are making sure that the fabric is in the right position.
When you look at this whole shape, the shape of the big body, don't just let the sleeves not participate first.
First determine the effect of the entire body part, the body part, and then put the sleeves on.
Otherwise, the sewing line of the sleeves will affect the sleeves of this big body.
Then you change it together, and you have to change it here and there.
I don't know if you have heard of a story.
It's that little bear eating bread.
One day, the little bear wanted to share the bread with two little bears.
The little bear A shared too much bread.
Then the little bear B said, why did you give me a little less bread?
Then the little bear A ate the bread of the little bear A again.
At this time, the bread of the little bear B became more.
Then the little bear A said, why did my bread become less?
No, no.
Then the fox went to eat the bread of the little bear B again.
Then he bit off another piece.
At this time, the bread of the little bear B was bitten again.
He bit off another piece.
Then the little bear B said, ah, my bread has become less.
The little bear A is more than me.
If the pattern of this dress is the little bear A, and this sleeve is the little bear B,
I am the fox, you know?
I change here, change there, change here, change there.
Ah, the more I change, the more I change, the more I change, the more I change, the more I change.
Is it not enough?
So we first counteract the fox.
First kick the little bear B out.
We first care about the little bear A.
MD and Kou seem to be a family.
We are a family.
We are like normal.
We are sisters.
OK?
Only one is a clothing company.
One is in the CG industry.
Let's change this side curve.
Let him relax a little bit.
Then when you are wearing clothes, you must remember.
This side seam line tries to make it vertical.
If it bends to which side, then you go to sort it out.
Just take a look at this.
Whether it's the back here, the neck here, or the front neck here.
Give him a treatment.
The side seam line makes it straight.
Don't wear crooked clothes.
If you wear a crooked one, your clothes will fall off easily.
OK.
Because when we are changing the width,
In fact, the curve lines in your sleeve will be modified.
We are going to change it later.
There is also the shoulder.
Do this military outfit at the end.
Look at our military outfit.
The shoulders are all more than this.
The clothes itself.
If you want it to be wide and loose,
Your shoulders will definitely be a little bit wider.
So when we are doing it,
It's just that the shoulder line here is a little bit longer.
Just make it a little bit wider.
Then we can activate the sleeves.
Then you see.
Now our sleeves.
When there is no activation.
Is not it?
We just have the first one.
We stretched the shoulder line.
Then our sleeves.
If we don't change this end now.
Then is it that the sleeves are not right?
Right?
Because I added a highlight to him.
So he looks like he has light and water.
So now we are going to put this.
We are going to move this point up.
Or down.
Kids can think about it.
Think about it.
Is this point of my shoulder just now moving outward?
Now the point of my sleeves.
You can see.
You can see that there is a blue position here.
Is my point going up or down?
Too smart.
Kick over your milk bottle.
Yes, it's going down.
Because we are now going to make the line match.
Okay.
Let's look at the bottom of the page.
Is this point of the bottom of the page?
Is it two points together?
Let's look at this point.
Then these two points on the other side.
Is the bottom of the page going up or down?
The bottom of the page.
We can't see the other point now anyway.
Is this point going up or down?
Let's not activate this sleeve first.
If you activate the sleeve and simulate it together now,
it will affect it.
Do you know?
Okay.
Let's not activate it first.
Just change it first.
Then let it participate in the simulation.
Yes.
It's going down.
Okay.
This also moves down a little bit.
Who answered the top?
Answer.
Answer the top.
Let me tell you.
If you move it up,
the sleeve will go straight into the meat.
No.
Move it down.
Shrink this edge down.
Move this point from the inside to the outside.
It's the same as what we just modified at the bottom of the page.
Okay.
Then we activate the page.
You can see.
Our sleeves won't have that kind of weird problem.
Okay.
Then let's take a look again.
Let me show you.
Let me just talk about it.
If your sleeves,
if your sleeves,
when you do the A pose,
there's this kind of bend.
You'll feel like there's a fold here.
Your sleeves shouldn't be parallel like this.
It's like this.
If you bend it a little bit like this,
it's a little bit longer here.
You put it a little bit.
What I mean by long is this edge.
This edge is a little bit longer.
You follow this rhythm.
Let it go in a little bit.
Move this point here.
It'll be a little bit better.
Okay.
Now it's connected like this.
Is it a smooth straight line?
Okay.
Now we've modified the sleeves.
There won't be any weird folds.
When you use this kind of operation habit to operate,
your problems,
the ones you've modified,
the ones we've modified like this,
at least in balance,
in the position of balance,
there won't be too much difference.
First of all,
we need to avoid some weird folds here.
But if you do it the other way around,
if you just want to have some weird folds here,
you can change it the other way around.
You can make the line here a little longer.
What we're talking about now is,
in most cases,
you just change the sleeves like this.
You don't want them to affect each other.
If they affect each other,
you just want to eat bread.
It won't work.
Next, we'll make a sleeve plate for it.
And sew it on.
After sewing it on,
because the sleeve plate is tight,
it can block out some folds.
Then we'll freeze the sleeve plate.
Then change the fabric.
Here,
our jacket can be used first.
We'll use this canvas fabric.
The fabric of the canvas fabric is quite hard.
It's easy to have big,
hard folds.
I'll go get some water.
Wait a minute.
Hello.
Yeah.
Okay.
Then activate the sleeve plate.
This is our sleeve.
Because later we will change the model's posture.
The frozen,
the frozen plate,
it can't follow the virtual model.
It will be frozen in the three-dimensional space.
Like our sleeve,
we need to give it,
because my water bottle is right next to it.
Like our sleeve,
it needs to be fixed to the wrist.
So,
we'll use a method to fix it.
That is,
we can draw a measurement line.
Then put this side
on the measurement line.
Stick it on.
Use this copy to the symmetrical position.
First,
let's create a copy of the position.
Then stick them on.
Okay.
After sticking it on,
you can see.
I'm here.
This is the position.
It will always be stuck here.
It won't fall down.
Okay.
We don't have time to rest
in the live broadcast tonight.
I will talk about it from the beginning to the end.
So,
you can only go to bed when you have time.
Okay.
Now our sleeves.
After you make it,
we need to change it.
For example,
the position of the collar.
When making this kind of coat,
it is different from that T-shirt.
It will have a large part of the space
on the neck.
So,
when we deal with the neck here,
we leave some space for it.
Including because I will finally
make a scarf for it inside.
Okay.
Even if I don't have this scarf,
you can see that the position of this collar
is not very wrong.
This is what we need.
When making the collar,
don't make it too close to the neck.
If it is too close to the neck,
the coat will not be relaxed.
Okay.
This includes some of the folds
that we made before.
It's still the same.
We have a lot of folds here.
So,
you need to dig out a triangle shape.
Just move this point inside.
Just change it little by little.
Don't change it too much at a time.
If you are not sure,
you just change it little by little.
Okay.
Then,
I found that the position of the side seam is oblique.
we will make some changes to the D6 dress.
We will make it straight and straight.
Okay.
Including the shoulder here,
if there is any protruding position,
or long position,
we will adjust it.
Next, we will reduce the shoulder width of the collar.
Reduce the thickness of the head.
Take a look at the case
of the smaller shoulder width of the collar.
and then I was thinking about making a collar. What kind of collar should I make?
I thought about making a collar.
Before making the collar, sometimes I thought about it while making it.
Because I didn't have a concept drawing, I made it myself.
So when I was making it, I would think a little bit about what kind of clothes I was going to make today.
I also wanted to make a collar.
Of course, sometimes the type of document I made was based on
something that you guys haven't learned.
For example, we haven't talked about military clothes for a long time.
The last time we talked about military clothes was last year.
So during this time, someone was asking how to make military clothes,
and how to make this backpack, and these things.
I'll talk about it.
There is a live broadcast.
There is a live broadcast on the upper left.
There is a live broadcast on this live broadcast.
Send a private message to the backstage family.
I'm pregnant.
It doesn't look like it, does it?
Then, including when making the collar,
these curves of our neck,
try to make it smooth.
Otherwise, when we make a whole piece of collar,
if the curve is not smooth,
the collar will be stretched,
and there will be some ugly wrinkles.
This is what we need to avoid.
Also, including the angle we mentioned before,
try to be straight.
Don't forget.
Next, we choose the two lines of the collar,
and then you can see its length
in the attribute editor next to it.
Then, based on this length,
draw a square.
Draw a square,
and then sew it.
Then we need to put this clothing panel first,
After sewing, create a symmetrical panel,
and then arrange this collar file.
After the collar is arranged,
you can see that my collar itself is a little stretched.
It's because we're using a cloth right now.
The physical properties of cloth fabric
is that it's not easy to stretch.
In other words, it doesn't have the elasticity.
The fabric itself is relatively hard,
and it is relatively easy to have its own support.
Secondly, its bending strength is also relatively high.
The bending strength is relatively high,
which means that it is not easy to bend.
In this way,
it will further strengthen the effect that it is easy to stand up.
The long-shape, the long-shape, okay?
Did I just say it in a square shape?
The long-shape panel.
Okay.
Then our collar.
Let's take a look now.
In the case that we don't modify any of the panels,
this collar,
is it protruding from the top here?
We need to make the collar have some
effect that can buckle up.
So,
are we going to shorten the length of this circle
that is close to the eye now?
Right?
Because when we do it at the end,
although when I look at it like this,
it's open.
But in the end,
it should be attached to the neck.
It should be one that will gradually
shrink up.
So we're going to shorten this side.
Shorten this side first.
After shortening,
will this corner become a sharp corner?
This is a sharp corner.
I've mentioned it to you before.
Don't let this corner be a sharp corner.
We're going to change it to a straight corner.
Otherwise,
it will be in a balanced position.
Look here.
Is this a sharp corner?
This is also a sharp corner.
It can't be straightened.
Then we'll put a zipper on it later.
Wouldn't that be worse?
Right?
So what are we going to change this corner now?
Change to a straight corner.
Do you understand?
This is also why I told you
that you must remember to
pay attention to it
when you do it.
Yes,
don't fake it.
It's really hard to fake it.
You must take care of your body.
The body is the most important thing.
Okay,
now we use the extension tool.
You can extend it.
If you extend it,
because after extending it,
the bottom here,
it will be longer.
We are extending it to the middle.
If you extend it to the middle,
it will shrink up.
These two sides are also nails.
It's like digging a V-shaped area in the middle.
Then change it to a curve point.
Now its collar is also straightened.
Then it is the upper eye.
It's more inner-closed here.
Do you understand?
Little friends,
remember to give me some feedback.
Don't not give me feedback.
My hands will shake.
Okay,
then we draw the inner line.
Put on the zipper for him.
If you put on the zipper here,
we will delete the part
that cuts out.
There will be a joint.
Okay,
because of the zipper,
we are the zipper.
Finally, it is convenient for us to do this.
If you look at the material picture,
it must be a rectangular version.
It's more convenient to make a zipper.
So let's replace the zipper here.
Sew it.
Then the physical attribute of the zipper
is the physical attribute of the hardware.
Change a zipper here.
Write the name for him.
This is what I want to say.
When you can't see it,
you must remember to change its name in time.
I have a habit.
I always don't like to change this name.
At the end,
when I was making the material,
I was so angry.
I said,
if I knew it earlier,
I would have named it earlier.
Because the name inside is
Fabric123456789.
I really can't stand it.
And then,
because we are doing
this kind of multi-layered clothing,
especially like this,
when it's a relatively loose dress,
we will make it two layers in and out.
Not just one layer.
Because our current version
is cut in the back here.
So the first thing we have to do
is to merge it first.
After merging,
because we want to do
the colon layer,
the colon to the outside,
this version is not possible.
Try not to let it be left and right.
This is called symmetrical editing.
This is Marvellous Designer 12.
12.
Sometimes,
in our...
Oops.
Sometimes,
in our group,
I will see
someone
who is still using
Marvellous Designer 8
asking me questions.
I really can't stand it.
This is...
Marvellous Designer 8
is really a very old version.
Everyone just
use the new version.
The new version,
we have a lot of new features.
This is Marvellous Designer 8.
Remember to delete the colon after merging.
The project requires Marvellous Designer 8.
It's too old.
The project,
the project requirements are too old.
How can you use Marvellous Designer 8?
This is a little too old.
Remember to merge here too.
Cancel the colon.
Otherwise you...
Because...
I'll explain to you in detail
why we need to merge first.
If we don't merge,
If it is not parallel, then these two panels are separate panels, then we are creating a column layer, that is, when doing this column layer structure, what will the column layer be like?
It will automatically create this powder line along all the lines on this panel, which will create a powder line in and out of two layers, and there will be a seam line in the middle of this split position.
If you want to break this powder line, then you have to create this powder line manually, isn't it one step more?
So we need to merge it first, merge it into a complete version, and then make it a column layer.
Otherwise, there will be a powder line here in the middle of this broken line.
Of course, if you want to modify and repair it afterwards, it is also very simple.
Just say,
It's faster and more convenient to do this way.
Then you can see that I have some internal lines that will be added to it during the production process.
So when we are doing the column layer, these internal lines will also automatically generate a powder line.
The function of the powder line is that it will have some influence on the shape of these folds of the fabric.
The position of the sewing line is also drawn with the internal line first.
And I think that after drawing the internal line, you will have a clearer understanding of this structure yourself.
Marlowe's Designer 12 can open the documents of Marlowe's Designer 9.
Thank you, two people, thank you.
I'm not working overtime.
I'm just our company.
To talk about our company's overtime is rarely overtime.
So like me, if I teach at night, we work in the afternoon.
And our company has a longer office time.
So if you are interested in joining our company, you can send me an resume.
Make an advertisement.
Then we will do some cutting.
Cutting and adjustment of these panels.
And those internal lines.
Because I was looking at those military uniforms.
There are quite a lot of military uniforms.
There are some unknown traps.
I don't know why I made a cut in this place.
So I also made some cuts like this.
Although I originally wanted to teach this military uniform.
But because it has to be in line with the theme of the Lantern Festival.
So I made a honeycomb.
Okay.
Since we are talking about cutting.
In fact, sometimes you are in a 3D window.
It's also very fast to cut directly with the shape line tool.
Oh, it turned out to be like this.
It's actually to deal with the wound.
I got it.
I know.
Then you can cut and sew directly with the editing shape line tool.
It's very fast.
And because it is.
Well, when you draw it, it cuts directly.
So you just hide the other extra panels.
After that, it will be cut by hand.
The company is in Shanghai Caojin.
No, the headquarters is in Korea.
But there is also in Shanghai.
I am working in Shanghai now.
After cutting.
Remember, if there is an automatic cut of the wound line.
I will seal it manually.